Guide to the North Carolina Council of Churches records, 1935-2019 RL.00934
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession (2007-0133), 11 boxes
  - Executive board meeting files
    - November 22, 1977 (Box 8)
    - October 17, 1977 (Box 8)
    - May 1977 (Box 9)
    - April 18, 1977 (Box 9)
    - November 18, 1976 (Box 9)
    - May 1976 (Box 9)
    - November 1975 (Box 9)
    - May 1974 (Box 9)
    - November 1973 (Box 9)
    - March 27, 1973 (Box 9)
    - November 1972 (Box 9)
    - May 19, 1972 (Box 9)
    - January 19, 1972 (Box 9)
    - October 21, 1971 (Box 9)
    - May 1971 (Box 10)
    - November 1970 (Box 10)
    - May 21, 1970 (Box 10)
    - March 9, 1970 (Box 10)
    - February 10, 1970 (Box 10)
    - November 18, 1969 (Box 10)
    - June 10, 1969 (Box 10)
    - March 19, 1969 (Box 10)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 10)
    - November 1967 (Box 10)
    - April-May 1967 (Box 10)
    - Minutes and reports, 1964-1965 (Box 11)
- Accession (2020-0094), 1947-2019; 2 boxes
  Scope and Contents
  Administrative records of the Church Women United in North Carolina/United Church Women/Church Women United, formerly NC Council of Church Women, including constitutions and bylaws, meetings minutes, reports, directories, newsletters, program files, financial records, clippings, and photographs.
  - Church Women United records, 1947-2013 (Box 1)
  - Church Women United records, 2014-2020 (Box 2)
  - Newsletters, State Assembly, Leaders' Council, and Local Units, 1967-2019 (Box 2)